export const data= [

    {
      question:"What is ICTC?",
      answer: "Inner Circle Trading Club is basically a group of private individuals coming together to earn passive income monthly through a sustainable and consistent financial market trading strategy/system.",
  
    },

    {
      question:"  What benefits come with an Inner Circle Trading Club membership?",
       answer: "  Being a member of Inner Circle Trading Club automatically grants you access to our world-class tested, and proven trading system built around synthetic indices trading that is less risky and devoid of external influences that affect market volatility in other financial markets."
      },



      {
        question:" Can I refer someone?",
         answer: " Yes you can. You earn 5% instant referral bonus(es) on your referral’s deposits. For example, you referred someone who deposits $1000, u earn $50 instant thank you referral bonus from ICTC."
        },

        {
          question:" What is the expected monthly profit?",
           answer: "  30% of the capital amount is what you earn monthly (30-day cycle). So, for example, if you deposited $1,000 on the 1st of October, by the 1st of November, you will have $300 (30% of $1000) available for you to withdraw.?"
          },



          {
            question:" Is my capital at risk?",

          answer: " We pride ourselves on our well-tested/proven money management system. This ensures we don't expose deposited funds by more than 5% to 10% at all times, while at the same time targeting profits in the range of 10% to 30%. This allows us to always come out on top with profits, no matter the losses encountered during a trading period."
            },



            {
              question:" Is there a fee for Inner Circle Trading Club membership?",
               answer: "  No, it’s 100% free to join our club."
              },


              {
                question:"  Can I track my deposits in real time?",
               
                answer: " Yes, we have been doing this for a long time now. Our confidence level therefore allows us to share our trading account password with all our private club members so that they can see what's going on in trades on a daily/weekly/monthly basis in real time. You get this trading account password within 3 days after your capital deposit is credited to the trading account."
                },

  
    {
    question:" Can I withdraw my earnings before the end of the month?",
     answer: " No, all profits are withdrawn after every 30-day cycle, no matter when your deposits come into the trading account. For example, if you deposited $1,000 on the 1st of October, by the 1st of November, you will have $300 (30% of $1000) available for you as your withdrawable profit. Kindly fill out the ICTC members form after making your deposit so that we have a proper documentation of your deposit and for prompt withdrawals on due date."
    },

    {
      question: "What deposit methods are accepted?",
      answer: "All deposits are to be made using USDT TRC 20. Note: Every deposit incurs a 5% broker fee, so please remember to add this when making your deposits."
    },

    {
      question: "Do you provide services too?",
      answer: ", Shoe-makers, Cobblers, Models, Make-up artists, Jewelers, Fashion-photographers, Fashion journalists, Logistics personnels, Influencers and so on. Our goal is to provide a platform that offers a diverse selection of fashion services for our users.",
  
    },
    {
      question: "Can I add to my deposit?",
      answer: " We have a limited amount we can handle at this private club stage. Kindly ask any of our admins per time if there is any space for a new deposit at all times before proceeding with your deposit."  
    },
    
    {
      question: "What benefits come with an Inner Circle Trading Club membership?",
      answer: "Being a member of Inner Circle Trading Club automatically grants you access to our world-class tested, and proven trading system built around synthetic indices trading that is less risky and devoid of external influences that affect market volatility in other financial markets."
  
    },

    {
      question: "What benefits come with an Inner Circle Trading Club membership?",
      answer: "Being a member of Inner Circle Trading Club automatically grants you access to our world-class tested, and proven trading system built around synthetic indices trading that is less risky and devoid of external influences that affect market volatility in other financial markets."
  
    },

    {
      question: "Will my new deposit be vested separately?",
      answer: " Yes, every deposit will always have its own stand-alone 30-day cycle of trading/profit-making."
    },


    {
      question: "What benefits come with an Inner Circle Trading Club membership?",
      answer: "Being a member of Inner Circle Trading Club automatically grants you access to our world-class tested, and proven trading system built around synthetic indices trading that is less risky and devoid of external influences that affect market volatility in other financial markets."
  
    },


    {
      question: "Is there a dedicated support team for addressing members queries or concerns?",
      answer: "Yes, our dedicated WhatsApp group administrators are available to assist and answer any member's queries or concerns at any time."
    },


    {
      question: "Are there any fees associated with profit withdrawals?",
      answer: "Yes, there is a withdrawal fee of 5% associated with profit withdrawals. For example, if you withdraw $300, you will receive $285 in your USDT TRC20 wallet."
    },


    {
      question: "Is there a minimum or maximum duration for capital deposits, or can members choose when to withdraw their funds?",
      answer: "Profits can be withdrawn every 30 days, while the initial capital can be withdrawn at any time with a 2-week notice in advance. This notice period allows us to handle account closure and financial arrangements efficiently. Kindly inform any of our WhatsApp admins here for such notifications."
    },

    {
      question: "Is there a minimum withdrawal amount?",
      answer: " Yes. Since the minimum deposit is $100, the minimum withdrawal will be 30% of $100 - $30."
    },

   {question: "Will I get automatic withdrawals?",
   answer:" No, all withdrawals are placed manually from the broker's trading account."
  },

   {
    question:"Are there restrictions on the frequency or timing of withdrawals?",
      answer:"  Withdrawals are processed once in every 30-day cycle, and it typically takes about 24 to 48 hours for the withdrawal to be credited to the members USDT wallet."
  
   },

   {
    question:"Do you have any testimonials or success stories from current or past ICTC members?",
      answer:" Yes, we have a collection of testimonials and success stories from both current and past ICTC members. As part of our commitment to transparency and trust, we provide access to the trading account, allowing members to see daily, weekly, and monthly updates on our trading activities. This includes the success stories of other members who have benefited from our club. We believe in sharing real, tangible results with our community."
   },



    ]